Guide to the Larry Hama Comic Book Collection 1967- 2011 MSS.337
Fales Library and Special Collections
Larry Hama Comic Book Collection
1967-2011
Fales Library and Special Collections
Hama, Larry
MSS.337
8 boxes
Larry Hama is a cartoonist, illustrator, writer, actor, and musician who has worked in the fields of entertainment and publishing since the 1960s. This archive represents comic books and other publications spanning 1967 to 2011, with many created by Hama himself. Also represented in the collection are drafting materials for a variety of Hama's creative projects. (from Asian/Pacific/American Institute, www.apa.nyu.edu/)
Biographical Note
Comic book writer and artist Larry Hama (b. 1949) is the creative force behind comic book titles like G.I. Joe, The 'Nam, and Bucky O'Hare, but his creative influence extends to other titles and fields.
A third generation (sansei) Japanese American, Hama was born in Manhattan and raised in Queens, New York. As a youth, Hama hoped to be a painter and attended Manhattan's High School of Art and Design, where one of his instructors was former Entertaining Comics (EC) artist Bernard Krigstein. Hama's talent was evident from an early age. He was able to sell his first work in comics to a fantasy film magazine, Castle of Frankenstein, when he was only 16 years old. Upon graduation from high school, Hama worked as a catalog illustrator.
From 1969 to 1971 Hama served in the U.S. Army in Vietnam, an experience that would inform much of his creative work. After his discharge, Hama found a job as an assistant at EC, and joined the Basement Workshop, a grassroots activist organization in Chinatown. After leaving EC, Hama joined comic book and commercial artist Neal Adams' Continuity Associates studio. Along with other artists like Ralph Reese, Frank Brunner, and Bernie Wrightson, Hama became part of an inking group, collectively credited as "Crusty Bunkers" and known for their distinctive, rough-hewn style. During his time at Neal Adams' studio, Hama created Bucky O' Hare, a comic character that later went on to have a television cartoon series, a video game and toy line. He became a "penciler" working on titles like Iron Fist, Wulf the Barbarian, Planet of Vampires, and Big Apple Comix.
Hama became an editor at DC Comics in 1977 before joining Marvel as an editor in 1980, where he edited acclaimed titles like Conan and The 'Nam. It was at Marvel that he began writing stories for G.I. Joe. Although the GI Joe series was originally meant as a short-term vehicle for the Hasbro toy line of military action figures, Hama created engaging storylines involving complex characters and details based on his knowledge of Eastern philosophies, martial arts, and military history. G.I. Joe became an unexpected blockbuster hit. In addition to creating an enormous catalog of toys, the title inspired, and continues to inspire, a number of comic book series, television shows, and movies.
Other works to which Hama has made significant contributions as writer or artist include The Nth Man: the Ultimate Ninja; Wolverine; Daredevil; The Punisher War Zone; Moon Knight; Before the Fantastic Four: Ben Grimm and Logan; Savage Tales; Generation X, and Batman. Most recently, Hama has written a new G.I. Joe short series called Barack the Barbarian, a fantasy-parody based on President Barack Obama and other major political figures.
Hama is also an actor and musician. He was the guitarist for the band K-Optics and, in the 1970s, was seen in minor roles on television shows like Saturday Night Live and M*A*S*H. In 1976, he was cast in two roles in Stephen Sondheim's original Broadway production, Pacific Overtures.
Biographical Note adapted from the Asian/Pacific American Archives Survey (https://apa.nyu.edu/survey/)
Scope and Content
The Larry Hama Comic Book Collection consists largely of comic books and other publications spanning 1967 to 2011. A large portion of this material consists of comics worked on by Hama. In addition to published materials, this collection also contains original drafting material and creative work.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
William F. Wu Comics Collection (MSS.244)
Arrangement
The collection is organized into the following series:
SERIES I: Comic Books and Periodicals consists of comic books, magazines, and other published materials. It is arranged into the following subseries by comic book series.
Subseries A: G.I. Joe - comics are organized primarily by publisher, and further ordered chronologically by the date of the first holding for each title.
Subseries B: Wolverine - comics are organized primarily by publisher, and further ordered chronologically by the date of the first holding for each title.
Subseries C: Various - organized alphabetically by title.
SERIES II: Drafting Materials and Creative Work consists of original visuals, character dossiers, storyboards, and correspondence. Original order and folder titles have been retained.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
G.I. Joe (Fictitious character); Drafts (documents); Asian Americans -- Ethnic identity.; Comic books.; Comics (documents).; Magazines (Periodicals); DC Comics, Inc.; Hama, Larry; Marvel Comics Group
- Series I: Comic Books and Periodicals
  - Subseries A: G.I. Joe
    Arrangement note
    -Contains G.I. Joe comics -Organized by Publisher (alphabetical), publication date of first holding (chronological), title (alphabetical)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.1-5), June 1982- December 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.7-10,12), January 1983- June 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.14,16-20), August 1983- February 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.21-26), March 1984- August 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.27-32), September 1984- February 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.33-38), March 1985- August 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.39-44), September 1985- February 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.45-50), March 1986- August 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.51-56), September 1986- February 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.57-62), March 1987- August 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.63-68), September 1987- February 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.69-74), March 1988- August 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.75-80), Septmeber 1988- November 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.81-86), December 1988- May 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.87-88,90-93), June 1989- December 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.94-99), December 1989- April 1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.100-105), May 1990- October 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.106-111), November 1990- April 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.112-117), May 1991- October 1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.118-123), November 1991- April 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.124-129), May 1992- October 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.130-135), November 1992- April 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.136-141), May 1993- October 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.142-147), November 1993- April 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.148-153), May 1994- October 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (vol.1, no.154-155) (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - G.I. Joe Yearbook (1-2), March 1985- March 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - G.I. Joe Yearbook (3-4), March 1987- February 1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - G.I. Joe: Special Missions (vol.1, no.1-6), October 1986- August 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - G.I. Joe: Special Missions (vol.1, no.7-12), October 1987- August 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - G.I. Joe: Special Missions (vol.1, no.13-18), September 1988- February 1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - G.I. Joe: Special Missions (vol.1, no.19-24), March 1989- August 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - G.I. Joe: Special Missions (vol.1, no.25-28), September 1989- December 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - G. I. Joe: European Missions (Action Force) (3,6,10), August 1988- March 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Tales of G.I. Joe (11,13,15), November 1988- March 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - G.I. Joe: Frontline (1), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - G.I. Joe: Frontline (2), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - G.I. Joe: Frontline (3), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - G.I. Joe: Frontline (4), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - G.I. Joe: Battle Files (1-3), 2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - G.I. Joe: American Elite (vol. II, issue 0), June 2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - G.I. Joe: Declassified (1-2), June 2006- August 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - G.I. Joe: Declassified (3), October 2006 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - G.I. Joe: Special Missions Antarctica, December 2006 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - G.I. Joe (0,1), October 2008- January 2009 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - G.I. Joe Volume 1, July 2009 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (1), February 2009 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (2), March 2009 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (3), April 2009 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (4), May 2009 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (5), June 2009 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (8), October 2009 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (8), October 2009 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (9), November 2009 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (10), December 2009 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (19), September 2010 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (IDW Incentive) (19), July 2010 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (Volume 1), September 2009 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (Volume 2), March 2010 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - G.I. Joe: Origins (Volume 4), January 2011 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 2), March 2009 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 2), March 2009 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 4), July 2009 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 4), July 2009 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 5), September 2009 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 5), September 2009 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 6), December 2009 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 7), February 2010 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 8), May 2010 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 8), May 2010 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 9), August 2010 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 10), December 2010 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 10), December 2010 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Classic G.I. Joe (Volume 11), March 2011 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - G.I. Joe Best of: Duke, June 2009 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - G.I. Joe Best of: Hawk, May 2009 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - G.I. Joe Best of: Scarlett, August 2010 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - G.I. Joe Best of: Snake Eyes, July 2009 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - G.I. Joe Worst of: Baroness, January 2010 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - G.I. Joe Worst of: Baroness, January 2010 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - G.I. Joe Worst of: Destro, June 2009 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - G.I. Joe Worst of: Destro, June 2009 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - G.I. Joe Worst of: Storm Shadow, July 2009 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - G.I. Joe Special Missions (Volume 1), June 2010 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - G.I. Joe Special Missions (Volume 2), October 2010 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - G.I. Joe Special Missions (Volume 3), January 2011 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - G.I. Joe Special Missions (Volume 3), January 2011 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (156), July 2010 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (157), August 2010 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (158), September 2010 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (159), October 2010 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (160), November 2010 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (161), December 2010 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (162), January 2011 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (163), February 2011 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (164), March 2011 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (165), April 2011 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero! (166), May 2011 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - G.I. Joe vs. Cobra (G.I. Joe Convention), 2008, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - G.I. Joe: Canadian Convention Edition, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - G.I. Joe: Collector's Club Magazine (May 2010, August 2010, September 2010, February 2011), May 2010- February 2011 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero 25th Anniversary (4-6,11-12), 2008 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - G.I. Joe: The Rise of Cobra: Mission Dossier, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Subseries B: Wolverine
    - Contains: Wolverine and X-Men/ Wolverine and X-Men related - Organized: Publisher (Alphabetical), publication date of first holding (chronological), Title (alphabetical) -
    - Wolverine (vol.1, no.4), December 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Uncanny X-Men (vol.1, no.175) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The X-Men Annual (vol.1, no.7), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - X-Men Unlimited (vol.1, no.9), December 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Wolverine, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Wolverine (1,6-10), November 1988- August 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Wolverine (11-16), Early September 1989- Mid November 1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Wolverine (17-19,21,23-24), November 1989- May 1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Wolverine (25-26,30,32-33), June 1990- November 1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Wolverine (34-39), December 1990- May 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Wolverine (40-45), June 1991- September 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Wolverine (46-50), September 1991- January 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Wolverine (51-55), February 1992- June 1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Wolverine (56-57,60-62,64), July 1992- December 1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Wolverine (66-67,70-71), February 1993- July 1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Wolverine (72-77), August 1993- January 1994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Wolverine (78-83), February 1994- July 1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Wolverine (84-88,91), August 1994- July 1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Wolverine (92-97), August 1995- January 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Wolverine (98-100,102-103), February 1996- July 1996 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Wolverine (104-108), August 1996- December 1996 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Wolverine (109-111), January 1997- March 1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Wolverine (112-114), April 1997- June 1997 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Wolverine (115-117), August 1997- October 1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Wolverine (118,121), November 1997- February 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - The Wolverine Saga (vol.1, no.1-4), September 1989- Mid December 1989 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - What If...? (vol.1, no.7), December 1989 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Marvel Comics Presents (vol.1, no.39,88-89,136-137), January 1990- Late September 1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - The New Mutants (vol.1, no.94), October 1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Wolverine Annual 2: Bloodlust, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Lobezno (39) [Spanish], 1992 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Marvel Collector's Edition Presents: Wolverine (1), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Wolverine: Inner Fury, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - X-Men Survival Guide to the Mansion (vol.1, no.1), August 1993 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - X-Men Anniversary Magazine (vol.1, no.1), September 1993 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Wolverine and the Punisher: Damaging Evidence (No.1), October 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Wolverine: Blood Hungry, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Wolverine: Killing, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Weapon X, April 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Wolverine: Evilution, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Wolverine '89, January 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Weapon X (vol.1, no.1-4), March 1995- June 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Wolverine vs. Spider-Man, March 1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Wolverine '96, October 1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Lobenzo (vol. II, no. 5) [Spanish], 1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Wolverine (1,8) [German], 1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Wolverine '95 (vol.1, no.1), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Logan: Path of the Warlord (vol.1, no.1), February 1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - X-Men '96, November 1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Wolverine Encyclopedia (vol. 1-2), November 1996- December 1996 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Team X/ Team 7, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Maverick (vol.1, no.1), January 1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Ballistic/ Wolverine (vol.1, #1), February 1997 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Wolverine Flashback (vol.1, no.1), July 1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - X-Men (vol.1, no.68), October 1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Generation X (vol.1, no.33-38), December 1997- May 1998 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Marvel Chillers: The Thing in the Glass Case, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Generation X (vol.1, no.39-42,46-47), June 1998- January 1999 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - J2 (vol.1, no.5), February 1999 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Wild Thing (vol.1, no. 1-5), October 1999- February 2000 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Before the Fantastic Four: Ben Grimm and Logan (vol.1, no.1-3), July 2000- September 2000 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Wolverine Legends Vol. 6: Marc Silvestri Book 1, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - X-Men: Age of Apocalypse One Shot (1), May 2005 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Wolverine: Saudade, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - X-Men: The Complete Onslaught Epic Book 2, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Deathblow/ Wolverine (1) [Canadian], September 1996 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Dolmen (9-10) [Spanish], August/ September 1996- Noviembre 1996 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Subseries C: Various
    - Contains miscellaneous comics-- both related to Hama in some capacity, as well as some in his personal collection - Organized by title (alphabetically), and by vol/ date of publication of first holding
    - The Amalgam Age of Comics: The DC Comics Collection, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - The Amazing Spiderman, [undated] (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Arrgh (1), December 1974 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - The Avengers (10,326,328), 1981- January 1991 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Back Issue (16,43), June 2006- September 2010 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Barack the Barbarian (1), June 2009 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Batman (575-578), March 2000- June 2000 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Batman (579-581), July 2000- Septmebr 2000 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Batman: Gotham Advetures (18), November 1999 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Batman: Legends of the Dark Knight (121,122), September 1999- October 1999 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Batman: Shadow of the Bat (90), October 1999 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Batman: Toyman (1-4), November 1998- February 1999 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Bat-Thing (1), June 1997 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Battle of Antietam: The Bloodiest Day (Osprey Graphic History), 2006 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Battle of the Bulge: Hitler's Last Gamble (Osprey Graphic History), 2007 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Battle of First Bull Run: The War is On! (Osprey Graphic History), 2007 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Battle of Guadalcanal: Fight to the Death (Osprey Graphic History), 2007 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Battle of Shiloh: Surprise Attack! (Osprey Graphic History), 2006 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Beavis and Butthead (23), January 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - By Apple Comix, September 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Bizarre Adventures (28,32,34), October 1981- February 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Blaze (1-4), August 1994- November 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Blaze (5,6,8,12), December 1994- July 1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Brimstone and the Borderhounds, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Bucky O'Hare (1-3), January 1991- July 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Cable (16), October 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Chilling Adventures in Sorcery (5), February 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Comics Interview (37,38,40), 1986- 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Conan (4-7, 10-11), November 1995- June 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Conan the Barbarian (221,224), August 1989- November 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Cops: The Job (1-4), June 1992- September 1992 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Crazy Magazine (63,83,91,94), June 1980-- April 1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Crossover Classics Vol.3: The Marvel/ DC Collection, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Dakota North, June 1986- October 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Daredevil (193,355,359), April 1983- August 1996 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Daredevil & Captain America: Dead on Arrival, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Dennis the Menace (37), August 1959 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Detective Comics (736), September 1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - The Devil's Handshake, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Echo of Futurepast (1-3), 1984 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Echo of Futurepast (4-7), February 1985- August 1985 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Elektra (17), April 1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Esquire, December 1994 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Essential Man-Thing Vol.2, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Essential Moon Knight Vol.3, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - F [Magazine], 1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Ghost Rider/ Blaze: Spirit of Vengeance (11), June 1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - G.I. Jackrabbits (1), December 1986 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Hawkman (27), December 1995 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Headquarters Quarterly Magazine (4), Fall 1993 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Howard the Duck Holiday Special (1), February 1997 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - The Island of Dr. Moreau (1), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - International Designer Network (vol.9, no.3), 2002 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - John Carter Warlord of Mars (28), October 1979 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Ka-zar (13-14), December 1975- February 1976 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Kitty Pryde, Agent of Shiled (1), December 1997 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - L'echo Des Savanes (11) [French], 1975 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Marvel Age (8,34-35,40,56,86,93), November 1983- October 1990 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Marvel Europe, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Marvel Fanfare (2), May 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Marvel Graphic Novel: Conan the Barbarian: The Skull of Set, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Marvel Holiday Special, January 1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Marvel Premiere (16-19), July 1974- November 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Marvel Tales Starring Peter Porker the Spectacular Spider-Ham (vol.1, no.1), November 1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Marvel Vision (19), July 1997 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Men of War (8,15), August 1978- April 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Mort the Dead Teenager (1-4), December 1993- March 1994 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Nth Man the Ultimate Ninja (vol.1, no.1-4), August 1989- November 1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Nth Man the Ultimate Ninja (vol.1, no.6-9), December 1989- February 1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Nth Man (vol.1, no.10-13), March 1990- June 1990 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Nth Man (vol.1, no.14,16), July 1990- September 1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The 'Nam (1-4), December 1986- March 1987 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - The 'Nam (5-8,10-13), April 1987- December 1987 (Box 7, Folder 14)